dc.gov 2015-06-16

# Privacy and Security | DC

The District of Columbia is committed to protecting the privacy of all visitors to any of our websites through the following practices.

###  Collection and Use of Online Information

When you visit our website, certain data, such as your computer's unique Internet protocol (IP) address, will be automatically collected and sent to the servers that support our website system to help us provide better service and a more effective website. In addition, as part of these efforts, sections of this site may place a small text file (typically only a few bytes) on your hard drive to allow us to identify your computer. We will not attempt to read any additional information on your hard drive, and we do not combine collected information with other personal information to determine your identity or your email address.

In order to visit certain areas of this site, or to use certain services, you may be asked to provide personal information, such as your name, address, or gender. If you are making a payment, we may ask for your credit card number and billing address. If you decline to provide requested information, our ability to serve you may be limited. But you will still be able to visit the site and take advantage of the wealth of information it offers.

###  Secure Transmissions

Please be assured that this site is equipped with security measures to protect the information you provide us. We encrypt credit card numbers and other data that must remain secure to meet legal requirements.

###  Protection of Personal Information

Your individual identifying information will not be shared, sold, or transferred to any third party without your prior consent, or unless it is required by law. It is available to District web development employees only for the purpose of maintaining the DC.Gov web portal and improving the site visitor experience.

###  Other Sites

The District of Columbia's privacy policy extends to District government websites only. If you access another organization's website through the [www.dc.gov website](http://dc.gov/ "dc.gov"), you should read that organization's privacy policy to determine its website practices.

Note: The District’s Affordable Care Act website, DC Health Link, is found at https://dchealthlink.com/. DC Health Link is operated by the DC Health Benefit Exchange Authority (the “Authority”).

####  Privacy and Security Policies for Website

This privacy and security policy describes the DC Health Benefit Exchange Authority's (the “Authority”) approach to information that is obtained from you via this website ("Site").  For information about our policy with respect to the collection, use, disclosure and maintenance of personally identifiable information ("Personally Identifiable Information" or "PII") in connection with the Authority's health benefit exchange ("Exchange") operations generally, see our Privacy and Security Policy for Exchange Operations.

####  Privacy and Security Policies for Exchange Operations

At the DC Health Benefit Exchange Authority ("Authority"), consumer privacy is important to us. We respect your right to privacy and will protect the information we maintain about you in the ongoing operation of the health benefit exchange ("Exchange") in accordance with applicable laws, regulations and standards for security and privacy. As a reflection of our commitment to protecting your information, the Authority has adopted these privacy and security policies, which govern our creation, collection, use, disclosure and maintenance of personally identifiable information ("Personally Identifiable Information" or "PII") in connection with Exchange operations (the "Privacy and Security Policies for Exchange Operations").
